<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-01-10T01:14:42.870Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-01-10T01:14:42.870Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Interesting Typography Links for January 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=360711</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/typography-links-january-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T22:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every now and then, I find that I’ve accumulated a bunch of links about various things I find interesting. Typography is one of those things! Here’s a list of typography links to other articles that I’ve been saving up and …
8 Interesting Typography Links for January 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Headings and IDs for Your freeCodeCamp Blog Post Table of Contents]]></title>
        <id>61d6e37ad2d9de084285d220</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-headings-and-ids-for-your-freecodecamp-blog-posts/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T21:31:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post we're going to get all the headings from a freeCodeCamp blog post to make a Table of Contents (ToC) in Ghost CMS. I recently published quite a large post here on freeCodeCamp and needed to add a table of contents to the post. There's a really good]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keyboard Not Working? How to Fix Windows 10 Keyboard Not Typing Problem]]></title>
        <id>61d7e914d2d9de084285df19</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/keyboard-not-working-how-to-fix-windows-10-keyboard-not-typing-problem/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T21:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever sat down to write some code or browse the internet, only to discover that your keyboard isn't working?  When your keyboard fails to work, it could be due to:  Physical damage Dirt Filter keys Outdated or corrupt driver Low battery (if you're using an external keyboard). You]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Argyle’s Sick Mouse-Out CSS Hover Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=360113</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adam-argyles-sick-mouse-out-css-hover-effect/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T20:15:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was killing some time browsing my CodePen feed for some eye candy and didn’t need to go past the first page before spotting a neat CSS hover effect by Adam Argyle.
I must’ve spent 10 minutes just staring …
Adam Argyle’s Sick Mouse-Out CSS Hover Effect originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Not Equal – Does Not Equal Operator Tutorial]]></title>
        <id>61d74f40d2d9de084285da90</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-not-equal-how-to-use-the-does-not-equal-operator/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T18:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're learning the basics of most programming languages, you are bound to come across operators.  In this tutorial, we will talk about the not equal operator in Python and also see a few examples of how it works.  Operators and Operands in PythonBefore talking about the not equal operator,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Git and GitHub in a Team like a Pro – Featuring Harry and Hermione 🧙]]></title>
        <id>6181e65c8bcfae07ca4e068b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-git-and-github-in-a-team-like-a-pro/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T18:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you will learn how to work in a team with a central repository on GitHub. You will work on issues, commits, pull requests, code reviews, and more. I don't consider myself an expert on Git, but I have learned a lot about it in my first month]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Append in Python – How to Append to a List or an Array]]></title>
        <id>61c8aeac755c16082490b36c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/append-in-python-how-to-append-to-a-list-or-an-array/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T17:41:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn about the .append() method in Python.  You'll also see how .append() differs from other methods used to add elements to lists.  Let's get started!  What are lists in Python? A definition for beginners An array in programming is an ordered collection of items, and all]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 10 Network Adapter Missing – How to Install Ethernet Driver on PC]]></title>
        <id>61d7ed4ad2d9de084285df89</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/windows-10-network-adapter-missing-how-to-install-ethernet-driver-on-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T16:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Windows 10 and other versions of the Windows operating system, you need a network adapter to connect to the internet through a wired or wireless network.  Sometimes, you might get an error that your network adapter is missing. This can be very frustrating because you won't be able to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changing A Tire On A Moving Car (Or How To Improve Product Roadmaps)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/changing-tire-on-moving-car/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/changing-tire-on-moving-car/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Product roadmaps are often treated as a series of checkboxes. But they are more than that. In this article, Scott Himmer explains how internal partnerships, research, design systems, and regular touch bases can help make sure that your product roadmap is a successful one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Scott Himmer)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[useRainbow()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359823</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/userainbow/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T14:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I took a break from work and started some small, personal projects (toys). One of those small projects is potato.horse where I keep all of my doodles, visual short stories and jokes. Check it out!
However, this post is not …
useRainbow() originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rafał Pastuszak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latency]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2565/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2565/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Container Query Polyfill That Just Works]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=360320</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-new-container-query-polyfill-that-just-works/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T22:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an easy-to-use CSS container query polyfill now. You essentially conditionally load it and forget about it. Then write spec-compliant container queries code.
A New Container Query Polyfill That Just Works originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Pie Chart Using Only CSS]]></title>
        <id>61c63165755c16082490aaf2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-only-pie-chart/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T20:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pie charts are common components that let you show portions of a whole, and you can use them for many different purposes.  You will find a lot of articles around building such a component, but they typically either rely on SVG or a lot of HTML elements.  In this post,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I Turned Down a Six-Figure Salary in Big Tech to Stay at a Five-Person Startup]]></title>
        <id>61d21460a7001508889343d7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-i-turned-down-a-six-figure-salary-in-big-tech-to-stay-at-a-five-person-startup/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T18:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two years out of coding bootcamp and I had an incredible offer from one of the world’s most highly-regarded tech companies…and I declined it. On paper, it was the dream job. Heck, it would have been the most “adult” job I’d ever had in my life so]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real-World Machine Learning—PyTorch and Monai for Healthcare Imaging]]></title>
        <id>61d716e6d2d9de084285d794</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pytorch-and-monai-for-healthcare-imaging/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T16:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To improve your skills in machine learning and artificial intelligence, it is important to solve real-world problems. What better problem to solve then helping to save people's lives? Machine learning is being used more and more in the field of healthcare. PyTorch and Monai can be used to discover tumors]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Integrate the Material UI Data Grid in React Using Data from a REST API]]></title>
        <id>61d4d739d2d9de084285c147</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-integrate-material-ui-data-grid-in-react-using-data-from-a-rest-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T16:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Material UI's Data Grid is a powerful and flexible data table. It makes it easy for you to display data and perform out of the box functionalities such as editing, sorting, filtering, pagination and more. In this article, we'll discuss why you should use the Data Grid in Material UI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Search For a Fixed Background Effect With Inline Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=358917</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-search-for-a-fixed-background-effect-with-inline-images/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T15:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was working on a client project a few days ago and wanted to create a certain effect on an <img>. See, background images can do the effect I was looking for somewhat easily with background-attachment: fixed;. With …
The Search For a Fixed Background Effect With Inline Images originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Lazar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes on Josh Comeau’s Custom CSS Reset]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359736</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/notes-on-josh-comeaus-custom-css-reset/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T21:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently talked with Elad Shechter on his new CSS reset, and shortly after that Josh Comeau blogged his. 
We’re in something of a new era of CSS resets where… you kind of don’t need one? There isn’t …
Notes on Josh Comeau’s Custom CSS Reset originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a Component That Supports Multiple Frameworks in a Monorepo]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=360239</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/make-a-component-multiple-frameworks-in-a-monorepo/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T15:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your mission — should you decide to accept it — is to build a Button component in four frameworks, but, only use one button.css file!
This idea is very important to me. I’ve been working on a component library called …
How to Make a Component That Supports Multiple Frameworks in a Monorepo originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob Levin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ten Tips For Aspiring Designer Beginners (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/ten-tips-aspiring-designer-beginners-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/ten-tips-aspiring-designer-beginners-part1/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article (the first part in a series of two), Luis Ouriach shares advice that he wishes he has when starting out in his career. These tips come from his experience as a user interface and product designer for close to ten years, and if you’re starting just now, then read on!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Luis Ouriach)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunshield]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2564/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2564/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should CSS Override Default Browser Styles?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359880</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/should-css-override-default-styles/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T19:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS overrides can change the default look of almost anything:
You can use CSS to override what a checkbox or radio button looks like, but if you don’t, the checkbox will look like a default checkbox on your operating system 
…
Should CSS Override Default Browser Styles? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Underlines Are Too Thin and Too Low in Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359838</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-underlines-are-too-thin-and-too-low-in-chrome/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T15:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve encountered two bugs in Chrome while testing the new CSS text-decoration-thickness and text-underline-offset properties, and I want to share them with you here in this article.
But first, let’s acknowledge one thing:
Default underlines are inconsistent
Let’s add a …
CSS Underlines Are Too Thin and Too Low in Chrome originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Šime Vidas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jetpack Features We Love and Use at CSS-Tricks]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=360452</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/jetpack-features-we-love-and-use-at-css-tricks/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T15:28:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
We use and love Jetpack around here. It’s a WordPress plugin that brings a whole suite of functionality to your site ranging from security to marketing with lots of ridiculously useful stuff in between! …
Jetpack Features We Love and Use at CSS-Tricks originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Based Fingerprinting]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=360385</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-based-fingerprinting/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T21:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fingerprinting is bad. It’s a term that refers to building up enough metadata about a user that you can essentially figure out who they are. JavaScript has access to all sorts of fingerprinting possibilities, which then combined with the IP …
CSS-Based Fingerprinting originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Browser Extension]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359615</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-create-a-browser-extension/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T15:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ll bet you are using browser extensions right now. Some of them are extremely popular and useful, like ad blockers, password managers, and PDF viewers. These extensions (or “add-ons”) are not limited to those purposes — you can do a …
How to Create a Browser Extension originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Kölker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composition-Based Design System In Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/composition-based-design-system-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/composition-based-design-system-figma/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figma has advanced enough where it now supports some powerful concepts that can help with the flexibility and maintainability of a design system. In this article, Sasha explains why she finds the Systems Designer position so rewarding — and it’s not only because of how fast certain tools have developed to help her master challenges she faces in her work projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Aleksandra Nagornaia)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Throat and Nasal Passages]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2563/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2563/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thank You (2021 Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359698</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/thank-you-2021-edition/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-01T17:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year has come to a close and it’s time again for our end-of-year wrapup. The most important message is this: thank you. (thankyouthankyou)
Thanks for stopping by and reading this site. If you didn’t, I’d be out …
Thank You (2021 Edition) originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defensive CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=360073</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/defensive-css/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T18:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed nails it again with “Defensive CSS.” The idea is that you should write CSS to be ready for issues caused by dynamic content. 
More items than you thought would be there? No problem, the area can expand or …
Defensive CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Year, Fresh Desktop (January 2022 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2022/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What better way could there be to start the new year than with some fresh inspiration? Our collection of wallpapers for January 2022 is bound to put a smile on your face — and maybe spark new ideas, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Formatting Meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://xkcd.com/2562/</id>
        <link href="https://xkcd.com/2562/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>xkcd.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Web is More Gooder, and Other Observations on Today’s Web Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359941</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-web-is-more-gooder-and-other-observations-on-todays-web-tech/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T20:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m actually working on a talk (whew! been a while! kinda feels good!) about just how good the world of building websites has gotten. I plan to cover a wide swath of web tech, on purpose, because I …
The Web is More Gooder, and Other Observations on Today’s Web Tech originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Price Projects And Manage Scope Creep]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/how-price-projects-manage-scope-screep/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/how-price-projects-manage-scope-screep/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-29T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping, estimating, and running digital projects can often feel like an exercise in futility. In this article, Paul Boag explains why you need to start breaking your projects down into manageable phases and why that’s the best way to achieve significant benefits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Gatsby Themes For WordPress-Powered Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/building-gatsby-themes-wordpress-powered-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/building-gatsby-themes-wordpress-powered-websites/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-27T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you already built and published a Gatsby theme? In this article, Paulina Hetman explains how Gatsby themes work and what problems they can solve by comparing Gatsby themes with their WordPress counterparts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paulina Hetman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating A Custom Range Input That Looks Consistent Across All Browsers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/create-custom-range-input-consistent-browsers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/create-custom-range-input-consistent-browsers/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Range inputs have notoriously been a pain to style. Each browser renders the input differently requiring you to use vendor prefixes in order to create a cohesive look and feel. In this article, we’ll take a look at the quirkiness of the HTML range input and demonstrate how to style the input to look consistent across all major browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alyssa Holland)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful UX Guidelines, Tools And Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/tools-tips-resources-to-build-better-user-experiences/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/tools-tips-resources-to-build-better-user-experiences/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A meaningful user experience is what can set your site apart from others. But what makes an experience truly meaningful? And how to achieve that? The tools, tips, and resources in this post not only help you to come up with a UX strategy that works for you and your team but also to circumvent potential UX pitfalls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving Core Web Vitals, A Smashing Magazine Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/core-web-vitals-case-study-smashing-magazine/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/core-web-vitals-case-study-smashing-magazine/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-20T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to improve Core Web Vitals, a Smashing Magazine case study on how we detected and fixed the bottlenecks, and how we ended up with green scores, all the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Human-Machine Interfaces For Vehicles Of The Future]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/designing-human-machine-interfaces-future-vehicles/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/designing-human-machine-interfaces-future-vehicles/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern HMIs are transforming the way we interact with our vehicles. A car becomes a gadget that we use in a similar way as we use our phones. Users expect a lot of HMI, they even evaluate car experience based on the experience they have with HMI. In this article, let’s look at some ways to help us satisfy users’ needs with proper design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nick Babich &amp; Gleb Kuznetsov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billing Management For Your Next SaaS Idea Using Stripe And Azure Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/billing-management-saas-stripe-azure-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/billing-management-saas-stripe-azure-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In every software-as-a-service solution, user billing and payments are key aspects in the sale of services rendered. Let’s learn about Stripe and how the REST API can be programmatically used in serverless functions to manage the billing for an application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nwani Victory)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Touch Design For Mobile Interfaces: Defining Mobile Devices (Excerpt)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/touch-design-mobile-interfaces-devices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/touch-design-mobile-interfaces-devices/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before we can talk about how people interact, much less how to take advantage of that knowledge and design, it’s important to understand a bit about the history, the technology, and what today counts as a mobile touchscreen device at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Steven Hoober)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modifying Headers In HTTP(s) Requests In UI Automation Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/headers-https-requests-ui-automation-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/headers-https-requests-ui-automation-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To be able to modify headers in a testing environment is a great thing to have. It allows control over your application as one can bypass authentication, set cookies, and so on. In this article, Nafees Nehar explores some methods which allow modification of headers in an automation testing setup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nafees Nehar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>